She has undergone a cashless operation from ICICI Lombard
and the patient was operated by SM Yadav ji
and my wife
delivered at Samjine Hospital. My
name is Rahul Dudi, I am a resident of Bansu
and my aunt had her operation at
Sanjivani Hospital, Kotputli and the
staff here is very helpful and
all the work is done perfectly after asking.
Samal ji Yadav ji operated on my wife
and the delivery was successful
and she had a cashless operation from ICICI Lombard
and the patient is doing very
well. SM Yadav ji did the operation and they
behave well with each other and
talk to the patient like a good friend, asking
what is the problem and what is it. I request all the
people of Kotputli and its surrounding areas to come
here once and get treatment.
Here treatment is done using all the cards.
[Music]